University of Arizona Fine Arts Library Music Reference Files Collection, 1918-1995
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
University of Arizona Fine Arts Library Music Reference Files Collection, 1918-1995
MS 556
University of Arizona. Fine Arts Library
This collection contains subject files referencing musical topics including composers, music history, music theory, suggested repertoire for individuals and ensembles, and other broad topics. These files were used as reference files at the University of Arizona Fine Arts Library.
5 linear feet
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/ E-Mail: LBRY-askspcoll@email.arizona.edu
Restrictions
There are no restrictions on this collection.
Historical Note
These files were gathered from the University of Arizona Fine Arts Library where they served as reference files.
Arrangement
This collection of files is organized alphabetically by subject.
Scope and Content Note
Papers 1918-1995: This collection consists of the reference files kept by the University of Arizona Fine Arts Library. The bulk of the material consists of three to five-paneled 9 inch by 4 inch pamphlets pertaining to individual composer biographies, catalog of works, and other related information. Other items in the collection are educational and group-focused materials in the form of periodicals, articles, repertoire lists, programs as well as papers on a variety of musical subjects. They are arranged alphabetically by subject. Notable examples are various charts visualizing music history, an accordion chart, and papers detailing the music of Colonial America.
Access Terms
American Academy of Teachers of Singing.
Composer--Biography.
Music Instruction and study.
Container List
This collection is arranged alphabetically by subject title.
- A (1 of 2), 1945-1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- A (2 of 2), 1945-1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- B (1 of 7), 1930-1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- B (2 of 7), 1930-1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- B (3 of 7), 1930-1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- B (4 of 7), 1930-1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- B (5 of 7), 1930-1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- B (6 of 7), 1930-1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- B (7 of 7), 1930-1995 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- C (1 of 6), 1933-1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- C (2 of 6), 1933-1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- C (3 of 6), 1933-1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- C (4 of 6), 1933-1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- C (5 of 6), 1933-1994 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- C (6 of 6), 1933-1994 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- D (1 of 2), 1960-1993 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- D (2 of 2), 1960-1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- E (1 of 2), 1960-1989 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- E (2 of 2), 1960-1989 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- F (1 of 4), 1918-1995 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- F (2 of 4), 1918-1995 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- F (3 of 4), 1918-1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- F (4 of 4), 1918-1995 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- G (1 of 2), 1957-1986 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- G (2 of 2), 1957-1986 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- H (1 of 5), 1945-1993 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- H (2 of 5), 1945-1993 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- H (3 of 5), 1945-1993 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- H (4 of 5), 1945-1993 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- H (5 of 5), 1945-1993 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- I, 1950-1988 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- J, 1955-1979 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- K (1 of 2), 1965-1991 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- K (2 of 2), 1965-1991 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- L (1 of 2), 1960-1991 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- L (2 of 2), 1960-1991 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- M (1 of 10), 1931-1995 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- M (2 of 10), 1931-1995 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- M (3 of 10), 1931-1995 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- M (4 of 10), 1931-1995 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- M (5 of 10), 1931-1995 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- M (6 of 10), 1931-1995 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- M (7 of 10), 1931-1995 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- M (8 of 10), 1931-1995 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- M (9 of 10), 1931-1995 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- M (10 of 10), 1931-1995 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- N (1 of 2), 1966-1986 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- N (2 of 2), 1966-1986 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- O, 1963-1986 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- P (1 of 4), 1959-1992 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- P (2 of 4), 1959-1992 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- P (3 of 4), 1959-1992 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- P (4 of 4), 1959-1992 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- R (1 of 4), 1960-1992 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- R (2 of 4), 1960-1992 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- R (3 of 4), 1960-1992 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- R (4 of 4), 1960-1992 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- S (1 of 5), 1941-1989 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- S (2 of 5), 1941-1989 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- S (3 of 5), 1941-1989 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- S (4 of 5), 1941-1989 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- S (5 of 5), 1941-1989 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- T (1 of 2), 1958-1987 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- T (2 of 2), 1958-1987 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- U-V (1 of 2), 1938-1988 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- U-V (2 of 2), 1938-1988 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- W (1 of 2), 1957-1989 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- W (2 of 2), 1957-1989 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Y-Z, 1966-1989 (Box 5, Folder 15)